THEY WERE STARTLED
AND FRIGHTENED,
THINKING THEY SAW A GHOST.
HE SAID TO THEM,
"WHY ARE YOU TROUBLED, AND WHY
DO DOUBTS RISE IN YOUR MINDS?
LOOK AT MY HANDS AND MY FEET.
IT IS I MYSELF!
TOUCH ME AND SEE;
A GHOST DOES NOT HAVE FLESH
AND BONES, AS YOU SEE I HAVE."
LUKE 24:37-39
It's still dawn. What is it?
Somebody died.
Who?
- You know Cho the ginseng farmer?
- Yeah.
His wife died.
It's raining buckets.
Hey, where are you off to?
Somebody died.
Who?
The wife of the ginseng farmer.
That's all I know.
But she's so young.
You said it.
- Have some breakfast before you go.
- I gotta hurry.
Just a bite!
- Hurrying won't bring back the dead.
- But I need to go now.
I said eat before you go.
Come on.
What happened?
I said I don't know.
They think she was murdered.
What kind of bastard kills people?
Damn son of a bitch.
Someone died?
Eat up, dear.
Who died?
Eat your breakfast.
Bye, Dad.
- You're so late!
- Gimme a raincoat.
What took you so long?
Two people are dead.
Where's the captain?
- He went to Seoul, remember?
- Right.
- Hurry up!
- I'm coming.
I'm right here. Look at me, Heung-guk!
Let go of me! That's my nephew!
Jong-gu!
He didn't do it!
I'm telling you he didn't do it!
Hello, Sergeant.
Looks like he did it with this.
Jabbed him 20 times.
Holy shit.
What's that?
I don't think he killed him here.
He dragged the body back to this place.
Pretty brutal.
- That's Cho, the husband?
- Looks that way.
I'll be damned.
- And the kid?
- We took him to a relative's.
Why did he do it?
Don't smell booze on him,
but he won't talk.
He must be high on something.
Why else would he sit there like that?
What the hell happened?
Sergeant, how have you been?
That's my nephew! Let go of me!
That rotten bastard.
Couldn't he use the GPS?
Why do I have to guide him?
Isn't that it?
- Get the wire cutters.
- Sir.
Pull it back.
What's with the stench?
So, Cho was killed here.
What the fuck is all this?
So he invited Cho over, killed him,
put the body in a sack, dragged it
to his house and killed his wife?
A crime of passion.
Make sure you photograph everything.
Here, there, that stuff over there.
- Jong-gu!
- Get over here.
Sergeant, come over here.
Shit!
- Damn.
- That was slippery.
Oh, man.
That cocksucker.
What kind of twisted freak is he?
THE WAILING
Pretty scary, isn't it?
Scary, my ass.
Anyway, that's the rumor in town.
Who... told you that story?
Byeong-gyu.
That damn bastard.
Now he's blabbering to you, too?
But from what I hear, there's definitely
something about that guy.
- Like what?
- The corner store owner went crazy.
The guy at the mill dropped dead.
- And then Heung-guk, two days ago.
- So?
All this began
after that Japanese man arrived.
Quit talking out of your ass,
you ignorant dope.
Who are you calling ignorant?
Look, the test results on Heung-guk
came back today.
Apparently he ate
some bad fucking mushrooms.
What?
You know the ones that make you
lose your damn mind?
His blood was full of that shit.
There were tons
of those dried mushrooms at his place.
You really believe that?
That's what the results said.
- Never tried those mushrooms as a kid?
- Hell, no.
Eating mushrooms
wouldn't make you do that.
You saw that poor fellow.
You think eating mushrooms can do that?
But I'm right about the Japanese guy.
If everyone's talking about him,
it means there's a good reason.
What the hell?
Power's gone out again.
Fuck.
I keep telling the captain,
if he has money for drinks,
he should get that damn wiring fixed.
He never listens.
What the fuck!
- What's wrong?
- What the hell was that?
- Look outside!
- What's outside?
- Outside, that... Fuck!
- What's your problem?
What is it, man?
You check it out!
- Me?
- Yes, you! Damn it!
You want me to go out?
I'm telling you, asshole!
Get your ass out there!
- For crying out loud...
- Okay, I'll go.
Come on, hurry!
Shit.
Who the fuck are you? What the hell?
Stop, goddamn it!
Stop it, you dirty slut! You whore.
Eat this, too.
Damn, you're heavy.
- I'm getting too old for this.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Old wives tell me
men still get it up after 70.
Then buy me some herbal supplements.
I keep having fucked-up nightmares.
- What are you doing in there?
- Oh, hell. Shit!
Nothing! Get away from the car.
Don't open it!
- Don't open it!
- What are you doing?
For crying out loud!
STATIONERY STORE
Dad.
Dad?
Look.
How do I look?
Pretty.
Very pretty.
How long were you watching?
Huh?
How much did you see?
Don't worry. I won't tell.
So you saw. You saw everything.
No big deal. It's not the first time.
What?
- Here.
- What?
It's okay. Have a sip.
Hurry up!
Son of a bitch!
What took you so long?
Why didn't you pick up?
My mother-in-law fell sick.
You bastard, you always use her
as an excuse! You just took a nap!
No, I didn't. I swear.
Get to work!
Excuse me, ma'am?
What the hell?
What are you doing? Stop her!
Yes, sir.
Come with me, ma'am.
Get off me! Get--
Sergeant, get her out of here.
Back off, people.
What's wrong with her?
Oh, shit.
Please calm down.
That idiot...
Calm down, ma'am.
Jong-gu.
Get cleaned up, man.
Hey, don't beat yourself up.
Ain't your fault that you're a girlie wimp
with balls the size of peas.
Jeez.
Hello!
- Hey.
- Hi, Hyo-jin.
Hello, Captain.
- How are you?
- Good.
- You got clean clothes for Daddy?
- Yeah.
Mom got you clean boxers
and an undershirt.
Thanks, darling.
Take a shower.
I will. Go home.
You didn't even eat. Come on, Dad.
All right, get out of here.
Can't you see Daddy's working?
See you.
Goodbye, officers.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- Take care, sweetie.
- Oh, my.
That little brat.
- Seong-bok?
- Yeah.
- It just hit me.
- What?
- That woman.
- What woman?
The one whose house burned down.
I knew I'd seen her somewhere.
- It's the naked woman from last night.
- What?
The woman who was
standing here last night.
Crazy fools.
They didn't burn to death.
They were stabbed.
- All three of them?
- Yeah.
Freaked the hell out of me, too.
Prime suspect is the missus
who hung herself.
What the heck happened?
Beats me.
Over here.
- In here!
- What?
Give us a hand.
A little more.
Found it.
Idiot, don't touch it with your bare hand.
What the...
Are you a moron?
That's evidence.
He should've wrapped it in cloth
or something, right?
GOKSEONG POLICE STATION
So, she killed everyone?
That's what they said.
I'll be damned.
So, that's what happened.
Why did you call me?
Things are crazy at work.
Because of this case.
Remember what I told you before?
What?
How the Jap raped a woman?
What about it?
You filthy slut.
That woman.
- It was her.
- What the hell are you talking about?
The woman he raped is the same woman
whose house burned down.
She went crazy after that,
and used to run around naked at night.
My wife saw her at the public bathhouse.
She was completely covered
in rashes and boils.
Mumbling gibberish the whole time.
Are you out of your mind?
Byeong-gyu's got to stop that.
Talking crap to his gullible buddies.
You worthless bastard,
it was your theory in the first place.
I was just messing with you.
Who in their right mind
would believe crap like that?
No, I think you're right.
Can't be the mushrooms,
that doesn't make sense.
Gimme a break!
What are you looking at?
Get outta here!
What?
Ignore her.
She's been doing that all morning.
What a nutjob.
So, how about you check
with the local dermatologist?
See if there's a medical record
on Heung-guk or that woman.
Stop it, you tramp!
I can't believe this.
It's important, you idiot.
The rash.
The rash is the link here.
I'm telling you.
Come on, hurry.
Stop it, you could hurt someone!
COMMUNITY HEALTH CENTER
Oh, my.
You're really getting on my nerves!
Where do you live?
Are you from this village?
What the hell?
Stop right there.
Damn it!
- That lady killed them all.
- What?
In there.
She killed them all in that room.
What do you mean?
The old woman told her
she would die if she did nothing.
So a shaman did a ritual.
But the lady refused.
That's why she killed them all.
Are you a family member?
- I'm not.
- Then who are you?
- Come with me.
- Hey!
What the...
You can't go in there.
It's all right.
Hey...
Come on.
The lady killed them here.
The old woman got it the worst.
Her head was smashed open
like a watermelon.
You saw it with your own eyes?
Yeah.
- I did.
- How?
The old woman tells me...
the Jap is a ghost.
He was gonna suck her blood dry.
- The Jap?
- Yeah.
The Jap with the limp.
You seen him?
Yeah.
- How many times?
- Once or twice.
- Be careful.
- Why?
The old woman says
if you keep seeing him around,
it's because he's stalking you.
To suck your blood dry.
Wait here for just a sec.
Okay.
- Get your ass over here.
- What?
Get over here now.
But I just found the dermatologist.
I found a witness. A witness.
So get over here as fast as you can.
What the...
Where'd she go?
What terrible sin did you commit
to yell like that?
Are you feeling sick?
I keep having weird dreams.
Who's the medicine for?
Hyo-jin's not feeling well.
She couldn't go to school.
She's burning up.
Where have you been while she was so sick?
I was getting her medicine.
What's with you? Take her to the hospital.
What on earth was that?
Turn off the hose first. Moron!
Wow.
Now you show up to work?
Well... Hyo-jin wasn't feeling well.
- Now your daughter's an excuse?
- I'm not making it up.
- Did you find your witness?
- No, sir.
You turned the whole town upside down.
You think this case will be your break?
Seong-bok's been calling around.
That's your excuse?
Look at him. He can't even wash the car.
You're driving me up the wall.
Even the chief heard about your witness.
Whether you lied or let her get away,
you're screwed either way.
Yes, sir.
Damn, this is so frustrating.
Why the hell did you listen
to that crazy girl?
Not her. I'm talking about this here.
WILD MUSHROOMS KILL FAMILY
"Wild mushrooms kill family"?
What did the dermatologist say?
Was it the mushrooms?
He wasn't sure, so he referred
Heung-guk to the hospital.
Told you. It can't be the mushrooms.
It's not impossible.
Shut your hole.
You know that story
that Byeong-gyu told you?
He told me more than one.
The one about the naked man
eating the deer carcass.
What's gotten into you?
At a crazy time like this?
It's because things are so crazy.
You know the guy who witnessed it, right?
HERBS & TONIC
Over here.
You may not believe it,
but I saw it with my own eyes.
Look at this.
Can you see it?
Sure.
I got 22 stitches.
It wasn't because you got drunk
and fell on your head?
What are you talking about?
I'm too old to be making shit up.
You got proof?
Proof? Hell, yeah!
I'm not the kind to talk shit
without backing it up.
Come look at this.
Don't be too shocked. Here it is.
Look.
You see? Empty, right?
I stayed the hell away from the mountains
ever since that day.
Even put the store up for sale.
How is that proof?
What?
Damn you.
That's not the point.
The point is, when I woke up
and opened my eyes,
there he was, naked like an animal,
except he had a diaper.
- A diaper?
- That's right.
- A grown man?
- I'm telling you.
- Grown men can wear diapers.
- Nonsense.
Plenty of elderly folks wear diapers
because of bladder problems.
He climbed a mountain at dawn
because of his bladder problems?
Bladder problems--
What the fuck is this meeting for
if you're not even going to listen?
Anyway,
he had his face buried in the carcass,
his body covered in blood
and eyes all bloodshot.
Then, he looked at me
with his blood-red eyes,
and all of a sudden...
I haven't slept since that day.
- Since you saw him eat the deer?
- That's right.
- You saw him eat raw flesh?
- Sure did.
Wait, look here.
You see these goose bumps?
Why the fuck are you laughing?
Where does that guy live?
- Why, you're gonna go?
- I think I should.
Don't, you'll regret it.
This is just my suspicion, but--
You know how the villagers
have been dying out recently?
He's got something to do with it.
He's not human.
Give me his address.
He lives in the middle of nowhere.
You have an idea of where he lives, right?
It's hard to explain in words.
It's deep in the valley somewhere.
How much farther is it?
Long way to go.
Shit!
What's the matter?
It's there.
- Over there.
- I don't see a house.
Look.
Right over there.
Isn't that a deer?
So, you weren't making it up?
What have I been telling you?
Oh, fuck.
What's happening?
- Scared me.
- What you said.
What's going on?
You're good, right?
We're not good.
You gotta show us the house.
It's just over that hill.
There's only one house. You can't miss it.
You came all the way here.
Take us to the house.
Don't touch me. I gotta go!
Where do you think you're going?
I said let go!
Shit.
Hey! Mister. Mister?
- Mister?
- Are you all right?
You fucking bastards.
- We're sorry.
- Fuck off.
I'm gonna get your asses sacked.
You just wait.
We're really sorry, okay?
Fuck you!
You deserve to be struck by lightning.
Where are you going?
You just got hit by lightning.
Oh, no!
What's the point of taking
all that health tonic...
if you're gonna get killed by lightning?
How can something like this happen?
Some people never get struck,
even if they try!
But they say, thanks to all that tonic,
he survived.
Nurse! Nurse!
It's Park Heung-guk in 302!
You gotta come now. It's Park Heung-guk!
It's an emergency!
Doctor!
What's going on?
Can anybody make sense...
of what's happening here?
Let's go back to the Jap's house tomorrow.
There's definitely something
going on there. Definitely.
Hyo-jin?
Hyo-jin. Baby!
Baby!
Daddy's right here.
Daddy's right here, sweetie.
Look at Daddy.
Look at Daddy. Hyo-jin!
Open your eyes. Open your eyes!
Hyo-jin!
Look at me.
Look at Daddy.
- Daddy's here.
- Dad!
- I'm right here.
- Do something, Daddy!
What, sweetie?
Someone keeps banging on the door,
trying to get in.
Who?
A strange man is trying to come in.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hyo-jin.
Hyo-jin?
What's this?
You're all right?
Morning, Dad.
She's eating fish. She never eats fish.
Something's wrong with her.
I overheard what Hyo-jin said
to you last night.
I asked the old lady next door
to recommend a good shaman.
I'm gonna consult with him,
just letting you know.
Got that?
Okay. Got it.
Good.
- Hey.
Say hello. This is my nephew.
What is he, a priest?
Not yet, he's in training.
He's just a deacon.
I realized we can't communicate
with that man anyway.
You speak Japanese?
A little, just a little.
He lived in Japan when he was young.
- What's that on your neck?
- Nothing.
You gotta be kidding me.
- What's your name, son?
- Yang E-sam.
- Is that your real name?
- Yes, sir.
Let's go. Get in.
Anybody home? Anyone?
What is it?
Goddamn perv.
Look at this. What does it say?
- Uncle, this is illegal.
- I know.
Then why... We should stop.
Get out if you won't help.
- But, Uncle!
- Okay, you wait outside.
What are you staring at? Don't be awkward.
Go keep a lookout.
What the fuck?
- Son of a bitch!
- Get over here!
Get him off of me!
What were you doing
poking around the doghouse?
Block the door! Block the door!
What are you doing? Block the door!
Shit!
Seong-bok, you bastard!
Fucking bastard!
Where is it?
- Where did it go?
- Over there.
Seong-bok.
I think it's the owner.
Seong-bok?
We're sorry.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
What's the matter with you?
Did you get bitten?
Say something, damn it.
He's the culprit.
You're scaring me, man.
Snap out of it.
It wasn't just one or two people.
He took pictures of them
when they were alive
and went back to take more
after they went crazy and died.
What the hell are you on about?
He's the culprit.
That's enough. We'll deal with it later.
I'm sure of it.
He...
He took his victims' belongings...
and did something with them.
What the hell did you see?
I said, what did you see?
JEON HYO-JIN
You're getting all wet!
- Where is Hyo-jin?
- In the living room.
Hyo-jin.
You're home early.
Did you lose a shoe?
No, why?
What's this then?
It's not mine.
- Isn't this your handwriting?
- I said it's not mine.
You know about a Japanese man
living in this village?
You're dripping water all over the place.
Answer me. Do you know him or not?
Did you meet him?
Answer me right now.
You're scaring her.
Leave us for a sec.
Come on, this is serious.
Daddy is a policeman. I know if you lie.
Did you meet that man?
Tell me.
Tell you what?
Everything.
Where you met and what you did.
- Why should I tell you that?
- Because it's important.
What's so important?
You're giving me attitude?
I said, what's so important?
What's so damn important?
What the hell is so damn important?
You don't even know what's important.
Stop fucking grilling me. Fuck.
HOMEWORK. JUMP ROPE. FUCK.
FUCK.
KILL. KILL. KILL.
What are you doing?
I thought you were sleeping.
Pulling up your daughter's skirt
in the middle of the night?
Why can't you speak?
Tell me, asshole.
Tell me, motherfucker!
Fuck you!
Stop staring, motherfucker!
Don't call your daddy that!
Don't you look at me!
Stop it! Daddy said he was sorry.
I'm gonna kill you all.
How could you?
I met the shaman today.
He says there's an evil spirit here.
It's possessed Hyo-jin.
He says if we don't act,
there'll be more deaths.
He's supposed to be the best.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Come with me, and don't give me any crap.
Ask him where he stashed the stuff.
The things in there... Where now?
What things?
He asks what.
The stuff that we saw before.
Things we saw before.
The photographs?
- You mean the pictures?
- Yeah, the pictures, and the other stuff.
Yes.
I burned them.
I said I burned them.
He burned them.
Where?
In the kitchen.
Bastard!
You!
What did you come here to do?
Ask him again.
Why are you here?
To travel.
To travel, he says.
Tell him I'll throw him in jail
if he doesn't fess up.
Be honest with us.
You wouldn't believe me
even if I told you.
He says you wouldn't believe him.
- You interpret everything I say literally.
- Yes, sir.
You fucking prick.
You loose-assed,
dog-fucking son of a whore!
So...
What kind of tourist hangs pictures
of dead people on his wall?
- Travel... The dead...
- Why was this in your house?
How did this...
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you?
I know what you're doing to this village.
I saw everything in that room.
And I know what the fuck
you're doing to my daughter!
I want you
to stop what you're doing
and leave this village quietly.
I mean it.
Just leave. Quietly.
This is Gokseong. My turf.
Don't mess around
and get yourself killed, just leave.
If you don't leave, you'll die.
If you heard me, say something,
or at least nod your fucking head!
Please answer.
All right. I'll prove it--
Shut up, bitch!
You're just gonna ignore me?
I'm just not worth answering.
Is that it?
You're not even gonna listen, right?
Ain't that right?
I'm speaking to you, but you won't listen!
You won't listen!
What's this? What the fuck is this?
What the hell is all this?
What the...
What the fuck are you doing,
a freaking ritual?
What the fuck are you doing in my town?
You know whose daughter
you're messing with?
- Son of a bitch!
- Look out!
Jong-gu?
Now what?
Believe me now?
I'll give you three days.
Pack up and leave in three days.
If you don't, you'll end up like your dog.
Interpret that.
Interpret what I said.
How long has it been like this?
Just a few days.
So?
The symptoms are the same as the others.
There's gotta be
an explanation for what she has.
They say they don't know.
- What is it?
- Oh, God!
Who the fuck did this?
Honey! Honey!
Get your husband.
Who did this?
Who the fuck did this?
Jong-gu!
Jong-gu! Jong-gu! Jong-gu!
Does he drink a lot?
It's nothing to worry about.
I'll take the needles out in 20 minutes.
Cut down on your drinking, if you don't
want to be paralyzed for good.
Okay.
It's begun.
You better brace yourself.
The thing we discussed the other day,
we'll do it tomorrow.
Where is Hyo-jin?
You can't back out now.
Get the money for the ritual.
- Where is she?
- At home. Where else would she be?
I asked the old lady next door
to watch her.
You left her alone with a stranger?
Are you out of your minds?
Don't move.
Baby.
Hyo-jin.
Baby!
- What's the matter?
- Oh, my God!
Hyo-jin! Hyo-jin!
What's this? Drop that, baby.
Don't cry. It's okay.
It's okay. It'll be okay!
Call 911! Quick!
This is all the work of that Jap.
Ever since we went to his house,
my body's been in pain.
I have bad fevers and I'm seeing things.
A man's face pops out of the wall.
I don't think it's a living man.
We gotta do something.
Or the bastard will get us first.
Shut the damn door!
What's in that jar?
Which one?
The one with a red lid.
It's just soy sauce.
Bring it over.
What, are you deaf?
Out of the way, come on.
Stand back.
What is that?
Fucking hell.
It's a real wicked spirit we've got here.
You don't want to leave, do you?
Let's go!
Stop it!
Hyo-jin!
Come here, you!
Did you recently meet something
you weren't supposed to?
What do you mean?
Did you disturb someone?
Of all the evil I've seen,
this is the strongest.
You disturbed it.
Oh, God. What can we do now?
Who is it?
- Who did you disturb?
- Tell him.
A Japanese man.
I knew it.
That's no man.
That's a ghost.
All the things that happened
around here are his doing.
If nothing is done about it,
not just your daughter
but everything that walks
on two feet will perish.
Sir.
This is Park Chun-bae,
the owner of this house.
- He killed his wife, too?
- It appears so.
What's that bastard's name?
Park Chun-bae.
Then what?
What do you mean, what?
Gotta get rid of it.
Either banish it, or kill it.
I'm going to cast a deadly hex
at dog hour tomorrow.
- Yes, sir.
- You got the money?
How much?
It would have to be about ten million won.
I'll have it ready.
Good.
Listen.
What I'm going to do tomorrow
is no ordinary ritual.
I'll be casting a deadly hex.
It's incredibly dangerous.
So, don't do anything that could taint it.
No intercourse.
Watch what you eat and drink.
Or the spell will backfire.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then, you can go.
Can I ask you something?
What?
That Japanese guy.
You said he's a ghost.
So?
I don't get how a living human
can be a ghost.
That's no living human.
He died a long time ago.
He must have been human once.
But not anymore.
So then,
the ghost entered inside him?
Well, that's how it started.
Not everything that moves,
breathes and talks is living.
Countless people have perished
because they didn't realize that.
If it's not stopped,
that demon will destroy this village.
Demon?
An evil spirit.
Even among demons,
he's a high-ranking spirit.
Well, then,
why... why did it have to be--
Why your daughter?
What sin did that young girl ever commit?
Yes.
If you go fishing,
do you know what you'll catch?
No.
He's just fishing.
Not even he knows what he'll catch.
He just threw out the bait,
and your daughter bit it.
That's all it is.
PARK CHUN-BAE
- This one?
- Not that one.
Money. Yes, money.
21,000 won more.
- I said no!
- That's okay.
What a weirdo.
Tell him to stop.
Stop!
I said stop!
Jong-gu! Jong-gu! Jong-gu!
What's the matter?
Look at me.
Baby?
Hyo-jin!
Please make him stop.
Please...
Please make him stop!
Dad!
Dad...
Hyo-jin.
What's the matter?
Stop, you bastards!
Stop! Fucking bastards!
Stop right now!
Stop!
I said stop!
Stop.
I'm gonna smash your heads in!
Stop, I said.
Get out.
Get out!
It all started from that day?
I'll try speaking to the priest.
Is what you're telling me true?
Yes.
You said the shaman told you this.
From their perspective,
a ghost is the spirit of a dead man.
But that man is alive.
I've heard about this man, too.
Rumor has it he is a renowned professor.
Some darker, disturbing rumors, too.
Others say he's a Buddhist monk.
But they're just rumors.
How can you believe them?
No, Father. They're definitely not rumors.
You sound terribly sure.
Did you see it with your own eyes?
How can you be sure
without seeing it for yourself?
Take her back to the hospital.
Trust the doctor.
Leave her to him.
There's nothing the Church can do for you.
Come with me to the Jap's.
Sorry?
I gotta see for myself,
whether he really is a ghost or not.
If he is...
then I won't be able to kill him.
Where is he?
- Is everyone here?
- Yeah.
What's going on so early in the morning?
Cheol-yeong couldn't come.
His sow is farrowing.
What's with your face?
You're not playing around, are you?
You're serious, right?
Yeah.
Cross your heart, or your mom's a whore?
You prick!
- This is no time for jokes.
- You fucking loser.
Go!
- Nothing?
- No.
Don't just stand around. Check the back.
What's that?
Fucking bastard.
Byeong-gyu! Over here!
Byeong-gyu! Hurry up!
- Is that him?
- Over there.
Where? Follow me.
Where?
What the...
Who's that?
What is that thing?
Don't come any closer. Back off.
Back off.
Stop it.
That's enough, man!
Sorry, man. Are you all right?
Stop it!
What are you doing to him?
- Something's wrong.
- Put it down.
- Let go!
- We can talk this out.
E-sam!
Dad!
Look.
There's another one.
That's him.
Get him!
Where?
- Son of a bitch!
- There he is!
Over there!
Son of a bitch!
Where is he?
Over there.
Where?
What's wrong?
- Come over here.
- Hey, why did you stop?
What's the matter?
Come over here!
Jong-gu.
Where'd he go? Where is that bastard?
Hey, man! Get down here.
Do you see him?
- Hey!
- Where did he go?
Jong-gu!
I gotta catch him.
Gotta catch the bastard.
Catch the bastard.
I can't believe this!
- Gotta save my baby.
- Come on.
- Let's go down.
- I gotta save my little girl.
- We'll get him.
- I gotta find him to save my baby.
Don't worry. We will.
Get your act together, man.
We gotta save her.
I know, man.
I know.
- I have to save my daughter!
- Come on, man.
I have to catch that bastard!
Don't cry, man.
Damn it, Jong-gu!
WIFE
Please, pick up.
Shit! Was that a person?
WIFE
The little ant...
fell into the trap.
Are you all right, baby?
You okay?
I'm okay!
Come here.
You're okay now?
Drink up.
Good girl.
Leave it.
I want to tidy up a little.
Leave it. We've got the shaman
to thank for everything.
Get some rest. You must be exhausted.
SHAMAN
Damn fool.
Suspect arrested
in the mushroom tonic case...
Victims have developed
severe mental derangement...
Mr. Yang E-sam?
Yes.
The victim is the landlady.
Your uncle must've taken the tonic too.
The town's been turned upside down.
We have to arrest him.
You should get him a lawyer.
In a way,
your uncle's a victim, too.
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
Get out.
MISSED CALLS - SHAMAN
What the hell?
What the...
- Hello.
- It's me.
- Where are you?
- What about you?
Just listen to me.
You need to go to your daughter, now.
Tell me. What's going on?
I'm at your place now.
Go back to your house now.
Stop scaring me. Tell me what's wrong.
I...
I misread the divination.
It's not him.
What are you talking about?
I cast the hex on the wrong ghost.
I saw a woman in front of your house.
I made a grave mistake.
A terrible, terrible mistake.
It's not the Japanese man.
That woman is the evil spirit.
It was all her doing.
So, go home now. I'm on my way there, too.
Then...
who's the Japanese man?
He was trying to kill that woman
in order to save people from her.
Understand?
That Japanese man...
is a shaman like me.
Was the woman
wearing white?
Did you see her?
A young woman?
That's her.
...defend us in battle.
Be our safeguard against the wickedness
and snares of evil.
Where is she?
Where's Hyo-jin?
Hyo-jin!
What is it?
Where are you going at this time of night?
I'm asking you.
Where is my daughter?
Where is she?
- Girl about this tall?
- Yeah.
Hyo-jin?
That's right.
She's possessed by an evil spirit.
The old woman tells me the Jap is a ghost.
- He's trying to suck her blood dry--
- Shut the fuck up!
Answer me, bitch.
Where is Hyo-jin?
- Have you seen the Jap?
- Where's my daughter?
At your house. Where else?
- She's not home.
- She is.
She just got back.
Don't go now.
Or you'll all die.
If you go now, your family perishes.
What are you talking about?
The Jap is waiting for you.
To annihilate your family.
He's dead.
He's not dead.
Death cannot touch him.
The demon will soon enter your home.
You've seen the demon?
At the house of the hanged woman.
- It was a dream.
- It was no dream.
I laid a snare for it.
Wait here until he is caught.
That's all you need do.
Hey.
What are you?
A human or a ghost?
Why do you ask?
I need to know...
whether I should trust you or not.
Trust me, and your family will be saved.
What are you?
Someone trying to save your daughter.
A woman.
I called all of her friends,
but no one knows where she is.
Hyo-jin?
Hyo-jin!
Baby.
Baby!
When will the demon come?
It's already there.
Hyo-jin.
It's already there?
Let me ask you one thing.
What is your true form?
What do you think I am?
The devil.
You are the devil.
Why can't you answer me?
You already said it.
That I'm the devil.
SHAMAN
I'm almost there.
Where are you? Are you home?
I'm with that woman now.
You must not let her tempt you.
Never.
Whatever she tells you,
you must go to your daughter now.
Do you understand me?
Understand?
Do you?
Is that your shaman?
Don't believe what he tells you.
They're in on it together.
Isn't that right?
You are already certain
that I'm the devil.
That's why you came here
with that sickle.
No matter what I tell you
about who I am with my own lips,
you'll never change your mind.
You're wrong.
Absolutely wrong.
You'd never believe me.
You came here to confirm
your suspicion about me being the devil.
That's not true!
If you say
that you're not the devil
and reveal to me your true form...
then I'll leave you alone.
When the demon is snared,
the rooster will cry three times.
Wait until the third cry.
You say you'll leave me alone and go?
Yes.
Two more.
Do not waver.
You'll just leave?
Yes.
I will leave you alone.
Who said I will let you leave?
Then, let me ask you one thing.
- What?
- So why...
Why the hell is he doing this?
Because her father has sinned.
What sin?
What sin did I commit?
Her father suspected another,
tried to kill him,
and finally did kill him.
But my daughter...
My daughter...
My daughter got sick first!
How can that...
How can that possibly...
One more now.
How can that be...
Don't do it.
What are you saying?
Whether you walk out of here or not
is not up to you.
"Touch me and see.
A ghost does not have flesh and bones,
as you see I have."
PARK CHUN-BAE
No.
That's not it.
- It's you.
- No.
This is all your doing.
- Don't do it.
- Hyo-jin...
Don't do it.
Hyo-jin!
No!
What are you doing?
Don't!
"Why are you troubled?"
Hyo-jin.
Honey...
Mother...
Look at me. Look at me!
Look at me!
Please. Look at me.
Look at me! Look at me!
Please...
Please!
Hyo-jin!
Hyo-jin! Hyo-jin!
Hyo-jin.
Hyo-jin!
"Why do doubts arise in your hearts?
See my hands and my feet.
That it is I...
myself."
Oh, Lord.
Hyo-jin...
It's okay.
My baby.
You know Daddy's a policeman.
I'll take care of everything.
Daddy will.